1800pocketpc.com 2017-06-07

# Privacy Policy

### Protecting your privacy is important to 1800PocketPC.com (also referred to herein as the “Website”). This Privacy Policy explains how 1800PocketPC.com collects, uses, and discloses the personal information you may provide while using the Website and the services provided through any part of the Website. It is always your choice whether or not to provide personal information through the Website. Any personal information you provide will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

1800PocketPC.COM IS OFFERED TO YOU, THE — USER, CONDITIONED ON YOUR ACCEPTANCE, WITHOUT MODIFICATION, OF THE FOLLOWING TERMS, CONDITIONS AND NOTIFICATIONS. YOUR — USE OF THIS WEBSITE CONSTITUTES YOUR EXPRESS AGREEMENT TO ALL SUCH TERMS, CONDITIONS AND NOTIFICATIONS. ANY OF OUR RIGHTS NOT EXPRESSLY GRANTED HEREIN ARE SPECIFICALLY RESERVED. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS HEREIN, YOU MAY NOT — USE OR SUBMIT PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THE WEBSITE.

### Information Automatically Collected

 _Non-Personal Information_

As is typical with most other Internet sites, the Website automatically collects certain non-personal information regarding users, such as the date and time you access the Website, your IP address, the URL from which you linked to the Website, the operating system you are using, the Website pages read and images viewed, and any content you post to the Website. This non-personal information is used for Website and system administration purposes. Non-personal information may be disclosed to others and permanently archived for future use.

When you visit 1800PocketPC.com, our servers also automatically record non-personal information based upon your usage of the Website. This information may include, but is not limited to, your computer’s Internet Protocol address, browser type, and information you search for or use on the Website.

 _Cookies_

The Website uses “cookies,” a technology that stores a small amount of information on a user’s computer to permit the Website to recognize future visits using that computer. Cookies enhance the convenience and use of the Website. For example, the information provided through cookies is used to recognize you as a previous user of the Website (so you do not have to enter your personal information every time), offer personalized content and information for your use and otherwise facilitate your Website experience.

Some of the banner ads that may be displayed in the Website may be provided by outside companies. These ads contain cookies. While 1800PocketPC.com uses cookies in other parts of the Website, cookies received with banner ads are collected by 1800PocketPC.com’s advertisers and 1800PocketPC.com does not have access to this information. 1800PocketPC.com may engage third parties to provide cookies that collect information regarding Website use. You may choose to decline cookies generally if your browser permits, but doing so may affect your use of the Website and your ability to access certain features of the Website.

### Personal Information You Specifically Provide

 _Your Personal Information_

During your use of the Website, you may be asked to voluntarily provide personal information (such as your name, or e-mail address for communications with you. If you choose not to provide certain requested personal information, you may not be able to use certain features of the Website. You can at any time choose to not receive such communications from us.

 _Use of Your Personal Information_

1800PocketPC.com may use your personal information (as described above) to contact and correspond with you, respond to your communications, provide services to you, facilitate and enhance your use of the Website, and as otherwise permitted by law. Additionally, 1800PocketPC.com may keep a record of all communications with you. You can unsubscribe from any such communications if you so choose.

1800PocketPC.com uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit its Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your search queries and visits to the Website and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

You should be aware that if you voluntarily disclose information online (whether through 1800PocketPC.com’s services or any other service available online), personal or otherwise, that information can be collected and used by others. For example, if you use forums or if you post personal information online, you may receive unsolicited messages from others. 1800PocketPC.com has no control over this use of your personal information and should not be held liable for any of its content contained therein.

1800PocketPC.com allows its users to send links by email and via social networks to other parties who may be interested in them. The Website does not retain any email addresses of either the sender or recipient of such articles or links after they are sent and only retains information provided voluntarily by the sender within the user profiles upon sign up.

 _E-mails and Messages from 1800PocketPC.com_

If you register as a 1800PocketPC.com member of any services we offer now or in the future, 1800PocketPC.com may send to you, from time to time, e-mail or other communications containing information about 1800PocketPC.com and other matters that 1800PocketPC.com believes will interest you. At any time you may ask 1800PocketPC.com to stop sending you e-mail by clicking the “unsubscribe” link included on the bottom of each e-mail.

1800PocketPC.com may disclose your personal information in the following circumstances and as otherwise permitted by applicable law:

  *  _ _Disclosure to Authorizing Persons__ – If you use the Website on behalf of another person or organization (such as your employer), 1800PocketPC.com may provide your personal information to that authorizing person/organization. 1800PocketPC.com has no control over the use of your personal information by the authorizing person/organization, and that use is not subject to this Privacy Policy.
  *  _ _Disclosure to 1800PocketPC.com Business Associates__ – 1800PocketPC.com may provide your personal information to its affiliated businesses, advertisers, or suppliers and service providers for use in connection with the operation of the Website. 1800PocketPC.com may also disclose your personal information to service providers who analyze Website use. 1800PocketPC.com requires its affiliated businesses, advertisers, suppliers and service providers to agree to use your personal information only for the purposes for which it is provided to them, and to protect the privacy of your personal information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.
  *  _ _Disclosure in Business Transfers__ – 1800PocketPC.com may be involved in the sale or transfer of some or all of its business. As part of that sale or transfer, 1800PocketPC.com may disclose your personal information to the acquiring organization, but will require the acquiring organization to agree to protect the privacy of your personal information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. 1800PocketPC.com shall assume no liability for the acquiring organization’s use and disclosure of your personal information. If at any time you do not wish 1800PocketPC.com to disclose your personal information as part of the sale or transfer of some or all of its business, please send your request by contacting us.
  *  _ _Law Enforcement and Legal Disclosure__ – 1800PocketPC.com may disclose your personal information to a government institution that has asserted its lawful authority to obtain the information or where 1800PocketPC.com has reasonable grounds to believe the information could be useful in the investigation of unlawful activity, or to comply with a subpoena or warrant or an order made by a court, person or body with jurisdiction to compel the production of information, or to comply with court rules regarding the production of records and information, or to its legal counsel. 1800PocketPC.com has no control over, or liability for, those persons’ use and disclosure of your personal information, and that use and disclosure is not subject to this Privacy Policy.

 _Depersonalized Information_

1800PocketPC.com may use personal information to create non-personal information regarding the use of the Website and related services. 1800PocketPC.com may then disclose that non-personal information to other persons and permanently archive that non-personal information for future use.

 _Business Contact Information_

To the extent permitted by law, the provisions of this Privacy Policy concerning “personal information” do not apply to information which enable you to be contacted at a place of business, such as your job position or title, business address, business telephone number, business fax number and business e-mail address.

 _Location of Information_

1800PocketPC.com does not store or process your personal information and makes significant efforts to protect itself and its users from unauthorized access to the data it does collect.

 _Securing Your Information_

To help protect the confidentiality of your personal information, 1800PocketPC.com employs reasonable security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. Nevertheless, security risks cannot be eliminated and 1800PocketPC.com cannot guarantee that your personal information will not be used or disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Policy.

 _Accessing Your Personal Information_

You may request access to your personal information and information about 1800PocketPC.com’s collection, use and disclosure of that information by [contacting us](http://www.1800pocketpc.com/contact-us/). Subject to certain exceptions prescribed by law, you will be given reasonable access to your personal information within a reasonable time, and to amend it as appropriate. 1800PocketPC.com attempts to keep its records as accurate and complete as possible.

 _Other Websites_

The Website may contain links to other sites or internet resources. When you click on one of those links you are contacting another website. 1800PocketPC.com has no responsibility or liability for or control over those other websites or their collection, use and disclosure of your personal information.

 _Former Users_

If you stop using the Website or your permission to use the Websites is terminated, 1800PocketPC.com may continue to use and disclose your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

To accommodate changes in the Website, changing technology, and legal developments, this Policy may be changed from time to time at 1800PocketPC.com’s sole discretion and without any prior notice to you. New versions of this Privacy Policy will be posted here. 1800PocketPC.com’s collection, use and disclosure of personal information will be governed by the version of this Privacy Policy in effect at that time.Your continued dealings with 1800PocketPC.com or your use of the Website subsequent to any changes to this Policy will signify your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with the changed Privacy Policy.

If you have any comments, questions, or concerns about this Privacy Policy, the Website, or your personal information, please [contact us](http://www.1800pocketpc.com/contact-us/).

Last updated: August 22, 2014
